Welcome brothers and sisters to the
Israel of God Wednesday question and
answer class where we open up with the
ten commandments that God commanded the
world to keep. Brother James. Yes, sir.
And God spake all these words, saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shalt have no
other gods before me. Thou shalt not
make unto thee any graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above, or that is in the earth beneath,
or that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. For I, the Lord thy God,
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me, and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me, and keep
my commandments. Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain. For
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain. Remember
the Sabbath day to keep it holy. Sixth
day shalt thou labor and do all thy
work, but the seventh day is the Sabbath
of the Lord thy God. In it thou shalt
not do any work. Thou nor thy son, nor
thy daughter, thy man's servant, nor thy
maid servant, nor thy cattle, nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates. For
in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in them is,
and restth the seventh day. Wherefore
the Lord blessed the Sabbath day, and
hallowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother, that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt
not commit adultery. Thou shalt not
steal. Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house. Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife, nor as
man's servant, nor as maid's servant,
nor as ox, nor as ass, nor anything that
is thy neighbors. I read Exodus 20:es
1-17. May the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word. In Jesus name we
pray. Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. So here on question and answer,
you can ask us a question and we will
answer it according to the King James
Bible. And if we cannot find an answer,
we will seek further counsel to bring
you an answer at a later time. And keep
in mind, all vague questions will not be
answered and all long scripture
questions will not be answered for
time's sake. But we may point you in the
direction of a CD or a DVD that you can
purchase by calling the office. We also
ask that you keep your scriptures at a
two scripture minimum. So for time's
sake, we we ask that you also be as
direct as possible with your questions.
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible.
No other Bible will be acknowledged on
this program. This is a live stream, so
if you have any questions, you could
submit them at this time. Let me
introduce you to the family that will
take part in the panel this evening. We
got Brother James.
>> Good evening, everyone.
We got brother Julius.
>> Good evening everybody.
>> We got sister Deborah.
>> Good evening.
>> We got brother Sean.
>> We got the guest caller and I am brother
Andre. And we will begin with our first
question of the evening. Sister Deborah,
what is our first?
Yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A. Uh,
Be Alert asks in Isaiah 35 versus
Ezekiel 20, the wilderness.
What's the difference?
Are the people fleeing the one with
knowledge in Isaiah and the ones being
gathered
is after Jesus gathers all Israel in
Ezekiel?
>> We're going to ask the guest caller to
answer that question.
We
>> the first thing is Isaiah the 25th
chapter 35th chapter is strictly talking
about the recovering of Israel to the
wilderness. All of them. But Ezekiel is
just a little different. Ezekiel
uh uh uh uh is talking about the
recovering of the people when Jesus
come. So we have two sets of people
that's going to go into the wilderness.
the first one of people of knowledge
that's described as a woman. We're going
to go into Revelation the 12th chapter
and we're going to read verse 6 and then
we're going to skip down and read verse
12 and 13.
>> Okay. Revelation 12:6 says, "And the
woman fled into the wilderness, where
she hath a place prepared of God, that
they should flee, that they should feed
her there 1,23
score days."
>> Now the Lord that that is the
wilderness. That's the place of safety
that the woman going to flee at. Now
skip down and read verse started reading
at verse 29.
Go ahead.
>> On verse 29 on Revelation 12.
>> No, no, no, no. We No, we don't. No, we
going to uh uh Revelation 12. No, skip
down and read verse 12 and 13.
>> Okay. It says, "Therefore, rejoice ye
heavens and ye that dwell in them. Woe
to the inhabitants of the earth and of
the sea. For the devil has come down
unto you, having great wrath, because he
knoweth that he hath but a short time.
>> And when the and when the dragon saw
that he was cast into the earth, he
persecuted the woman, which brought
forth the manchild.
>> Now he tried what was that?
>> That was verse 13.
>> Read verse 14.
And to the woman were given two wings of
a great eagle that she might fly into
the wilderness into her place where she
is nourished for a time and times and
half a time from the face of the
serpent.
>> It read
>> and the serpent cast out of her out of
his mouth water as a flood after the
woman that he might cause her to be
carried away of the flood.
Now, the whole thing is he couldn't get
her. So, this skip down to verse 17 and
show you what he did. Go ahead.
>> And the dragon was wroth with the woman
and went to make war with the remnant of
her seed, which keep the commandments of
God and have the testimony of Jesus
Christ.
>> Now, these are the people of knowledge
that make up this woman that fled to the
wilderness before the great tribulation.
That's why the Lord said when you
therefore see the abomination desolation
stand in the old place he that read let
him understand he told you to flee that
is before tribulation but 20th chapter
of uh uh uh Ezekiel covers the recovery
after the tribulation let's go now to re
uh Matthew the 24th chapter and we're
going to start reading at verse 39 29
rather from Matthew's Mthew
I'm sorry from Matthews 39.
Okay. So Matthew 24:39
starting.
>> Hold on a second. Let me make sure where
it say immediately after the tribulation
of those days. That's 39.
>> That's that's 29, sir.
>> It's Matthew 24 and 29,
>> right?
>> Okay. Verse 29, go ahead.
>> It says, "Immediately after the
tribulation of those days shall the sun
be darkened, and the moon shall not give
her light, and the stars shall fall from
heaven, and the powers of the heavens
shall be shaken."
and and then shall appear the sign of
the Son of Man in heaven. And then shall
all the tribes of the earth mourn, and
they shall see the Son of Man coming in
the clouds of heaven with power and
great glory.
>> And he shall send his angels with a
great sound of a trumpet, and they shall
gather together his elect from the four
winds from one end of heaven to the
other.
Now that is the time when Ezekiel the
20th chapter will be fulfilled. So the
35th chapter of Isaiah is talking about
the wilderness. Both the ones of
knowledge will go there first and later
on Jesus will gather all of the rest of
Israel and take them to the same
wilderness. Only difference is one would
before and one will will will be
recovered after the tribulation.
That's it.
>> Thank you for that guest caller, Sister
Deborah. Next question.
>> Next question. MJ asks, "Is there a
scripture that says the earth is also a
heaven?"
>> We're going to ask brother Julius to
answer that question. Brother Julius.
>> Yeah. Let's go to uh let's go to
because you got three heavens. You got
three heavens. the earth being the first
one, everything above the ground to the
body of water uh that separates the
third from the second heaven and then
you got the heaven of heaven where the
father, the son, and the holy angels
dwell. Let's go, Dre, to Deuteronomy,
the 30th chapter. Matter of fact, let's
stay right here in Matthew the 29th chap
24th chapter. Let's get it from Jesus'
mouth. Matthew 24. There we go. I got
two other scriptures. Matthew 24 and
uh verse 29 tell you about uh after the
tribulation of those days. Now we going
30 and 31. Dre. James Matthew 24:30 and
31. Go ahead.
>> Okay. And then shall appear the sign of
the son of man in heaven. And then shall
all the tribes of the earth mourn. And
they shall see the son of man coming in
the clouds of heaven with power and
great glory.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he shall send his angels with a
great sound of a trumpet and they shall
gather together his elect from the four
winds and from one end of heaven to the
to the other. Now if you do the uh read
the scriptures Jesus himself told you in
St. John the 3rd chapter verse 13 that
no man has ascended up to heaven except
Jesus he had a right to go back because
he came from heaven but when it says
right here this heaven is talking about
the earth notice what we the key word
he's going to gather his elect right
he's going to gather together his elect
from the four wind north south east and
west from among all the gentile nations
where where Israel is scattered from one
end of the heaven to the other now let's
look at Deuteronomy the 30th chapter.
Let's look at what Moses wrote. What the
Lord had Moses wrote. Deuteronomy the
30th chapter and we going to read verses
to 5. Deuteronomy 30 verse 3 to 4,
sorry, 3 to 4. Go ahead and read it.
that then the Lord thy God will turn thy
captivity and have compassion upon thee,
and will return and gather thee from all
the nations, whether the Lord
>> Hold on, hold on, James. From all
>> the nations.
>> Nations are on earth, not up in heaven.
Nations are up on earth. But go ahead.
>> Whether the Lord thy God has scattered
thee,
>> go ahead.
>> If any of thine be driven out unto the
outmost parts of heaven,
>> Uh-huh. From thence will the Lord thy
God gather thee, and from thence will he
fetch thee.
>> He's not going to gather you from up
above. He going to gather you from below
on the earth. Because we're talking
about gathering. So Jesush
what he said coincided what Moses wrote.
The scriptures cannot be broken. My last
place Isaiah the 43rd chapter. Isaiah
43.
And pick it. We're going to read five
and six. Isaiah 43 and verse 5 and 6.
When you get that, brother James, let's
go.
>> Fear not, for I am with thee. I will
bring thy seed from the east and gather
thee from the west.
>> Notice they keep talking to the east and
west. We talking earth. Go ahead.
>> I will say to the north, give up, and to
the south, keep not back. Uh-huh.
>> Bring my sons from far and my daughters
from the ends of the earth.
>> From the ends of the earth. Jesus said
heaven. Moses said heaven. But then
Isaiah said the earth. But it's the same
thing. We're talking about the first
heaven which is the earth. So I hope
that helped.
And Jesus told you no man has ascended
up to heaven except he that came down.
So only he going to gather his saints
from the earth, sisters and brothers,
and bring them unto his gathering place.
That's all I got. I hope that helped.
>> That's right. All right, sister Deborah.
Next question, please.
>> Next question. Alan Forlum
asks, "After the man of sin since it
sits in the temple, the will
build. How long do we have to flee? Is
there a specific time window to flee?
And Matthew 24 verses 15-1 17 are given.
>> Guest caller just addressed it a little
bit. He he addressed it with knowledge
you can flee. You can flee before the
great tribulation. But let's look at the
scripture Matthew the 24th chapter
because the Lord tell us through the
scriptures to watch and pray. Watch and
pray. Matthew the 24th chapter. Let's
read verse because the answer is right
here. Matthew 24 and 15. Cuz this is
going to be an urgent time for not only
people in that area but for people all
over the world who has knowledge. Go
ahead at verse 15.
It says, "When ye therefore shall see
the abomination of desolation spoken of
by Daniel the prophet, stand in the holy
place."
>> How do you have to flee? When you see
the abomination that make desolation
stand in the holy place. Go ahead.
>> Whoso readeth, let him understand.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Then let them which be in Judea flee
into the mountains.
>> Uhhuh. Let let him which is on the
housetop not come down to take anything
out of his house
>> because it's a time of urgency. It's
time to flee in because th this man
going to bring havoc onto all as our
guest caller said these are people that
serve God. Sisters and brothers go
ahead.
>> That was 17.
>> That's good. So therefore when you see
the abomination that make a desolate
you're going to see these signs sisters
and brothers they are going to happen.
Prophecy is going to happen. And so
that's why the book tell you that he who
has let him whoever whosoever read it
let him understand. But you got to read
and understand and be taught biblical
prophecy.
Just that's how urgent this time will
be. It's going to affect the whole
world.
That's all I got.
>> That's all I got. Thank you, brother
Julius.
Guest caller.
>> If you keep reading a little bit so you
can see the urgency of it. Keep reading.
>> Okay.
>> Keep reading.
>> Verse verse. Verse 18.
>> 18. Yes.
>> It says, "Neither let him which is in
the field return back to take."
>> You're muted, James.
>> Did you hit the mute button?
>> We can't hear you. Yeah, we can't hear
you, James.
>> I'll pick up verse 18. It reads,
"Neither let him which is in the field
return back to take his clothes." 19
says, "And woe unto them that are with
child, and to them that give suck in
those days."
Verse 20. But pray ye that your flight
be not in the winter, neither on the
Sabbath day. For then shall be great
tribulation, such as was not.
>> Now, to show you how urgent that is. If
he's of you on the housetop, don't even
bother to come down and get your
clothes. If you're in the field, don't
go back to your house to get nothing.
Flee immediately. So, when do you flee?
time you see this guy go into the temple
that's going to be built over there.
Don't wait a day. Don't wait a month.
Don't wait a week.
>> Bleed in.
>> That's right.
>> Okay.
>> Thank you, guest co.
>> All right, Sister Deborah. We'll move on
to the next question.
>> Moving on.
>> Excuse me,
>> brother James. you going to log off and
come back in.
>> All right. The next question Brit Brat
asks in Matthew 1 verse 21.
It stated that Jesus shall save his
people from their sins. Did this mean he
died only for the Israelite sins or all
mankind that were sinning?
>> Yeah. Jesus didn't just die for Israel,
but he is coming to save Israel, but not
just Israel. So, uh, brother Sean, if we
can, let's go to that Matthew 1 and 21.
>> Matthew 1 and 21. Go ahead, brother.
>> And he shall bring forth a son, and thou
shalt call his name Jesus, for he shall
save his people from their sins. That's
right. He is going to save his people
from their sins. But now, let's go to
John the first chapter and we going to
read verse 29 there. John the 1st
chapter verse 29.
When you get it, go ahead, brother.
>> The next day John seeth Jesus cometh
unto him and saith, Behold the lamb of
God which taketh away the sin of the
world. So, it's not just Israel, but it
is the sin of the world that Jesus taken
away. Now, let's go to John 3:16. And we
got one more after that. John 3:16.
Go ahead when you get it, brother Sean.
>> For God so loved the world that he gave
his only begotten son that whosoever
believeth in him should not perish but
have everlasting life. whosoever
believeth in him and believe don't mean
just yeah I believe him but we don't do
nothing he say believe is a action word
we do what we believe in so if we
believe him we follow his word now let's
go to Galatians 3 and we going to read
26-29
and that will be it Galatians 3 26- 29
go ahead when you get it, brother.
>> For ye are all the children of God by
faith in Jesus Christ.
>> Mhm.
>> For as many of you as have been baptized
into Christ have put on Christ.
>> Yes. Go ahead.
>> There is neither Jew nor Greek. There is
neither bond nor free. There is neither
male nor female. For ye are all one in
Christ Jesus.
>> Go ahead. And if ye be Christ, then are
ye Abraham's seed and hes according to
the promise.
>> So it's not just for Israel, but it's
for all that have faith in Jesus Christ
and been baptized and put on Christ.
Okay, I hope that that helps and we'll
move on to
>> guest caller.
I want to throw in one from the Old
Testament because Hebrews
>> smirks at New Testament.
>> Okay,
>> the seven 22nd chapter.
This is when Abraham, the Lord tried
Abraham and told Abraham to sacrifice
Isaac.
And when Abraham got ready to sacrifice
Isaac, the God had to God had to holler
and the angel had to holler down and
tell Abraham, "Don't uh uh do nothing to
the boy." In other words, don't kill uh
Isaac because now I know that you fear
God. And the angel gave another message
too from heaven. Let's start there at
verse 15 and we're going to read down to
uh verse 18.
Okay, can everybody hear me?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Genesis 22:15 says, "And the angel
of the Lord called unto Abraham out of
the heaven the second time, and said, By
myself have I sworn, saith the Lord, for
because thou has done this thing, and
has not withheld thy son, thine only
son, that in blessing I will bless thee,
and in multiplying I will multiply thy
seed as the stars of heaven, and as the
sand, which is upon the seashore, and
thy seed seed shall possess the gate of
his enemies. And in thy seed shall all
the nations of the earth be blessed
because thou has obey. All the nations
of all thy seed shall all the nations of
the earth be blessed because thou has
obeyed my voice.
>> That didn't leave anybody out, did it?
>> Nobody. No, it didn't.
>> Nobody.
>> Cuz this seed is Christ. That's why it
said in Galatians, if you be Christ,
then you Abraham's seed and hell
according to the promise. And this is
when the promise was made. Okay,
>> that is correct. Thank you for that
guest caller. We hope that you got some
un We know you got some understanding
with that and we'll move on to the next
question. Sister Deborah,
>> next question. Dborah Walder asked for
you to explain 1 Chronicles 21:es 1-7.
Why does David sin and why was this act
an abomination against God?
>> Uh 1 Chronicles 21 1-7. We're going to
ask the guest caller to answer that
question. Guest caller. Well,
>> let's go read it first.
>> Okay. 1st Chronicles 21:es 1-7 says,
"And Satan stood up against Israel and
provoked David to number Israel. And
David said to Joab and to the rulers of
the people, go number Israel from
Beerseba, even to Dan, and bring the
number of them to me, that I may know
it." And Joab answered, "The Lord, make
his people and hund times so many more
as they be. But my lord the king, are
they not all my lord's servants? Why
then doth my lord require this thing?
Why will he be a cause of trespass to
Israel?"
Nevertheless, the king's word prevailed
against Joab. Wherefore Joab departed,
and went throughout all Israel, and came
to Jerusalem. And Joab came and he gave
the sum of the number of the people unto
David. And all they of Israel were a
thousand thousand and a 100,000 men that
drew sword. And Judah was 400.
Pardon me. Where are you at?
>> Verse five. Go ahead.
And and I'll start from the top. And
Joab gave the sum of the number of the
people unto David. And all they of
Israel were a thousand,000 and a 100,000
men that drew sword. And Judah was 400
three score and 10,000 men that drew
sword. Verse six. But Levi and Benjamin
counted he not among them. For the
king's word was abominable to Joab. and
God displeased with this thing.
Therefore, he smoked Israel.
>> Now, let me show you why is because when
God gave said that Israel would be like
the stars of heaven and the sands of the
sea, they couldn't be counted. Let's go.
Now, you're in 1 Chronicles the 27th
chapter. Read verse 23 cuz David uh
didn't complete it. Verse 23. Go ahead.
And Oran said unto David, "Take it to
thee, and let my lord the king do that
which is good in his eyes." Lo,
>> hold on.
>> That was That was 1 Chronicles. We were
in 21.
>> 23.
>> Okay.
So, 1 Chronicles 23.
>> 27 and 23.
27 and 23 says,
"But David took not the number of them
from 20 years old and under, because the
Lord had said he would increase Israel
like to the stars of the heavens."
>> And that's why David didn't count them
all. Now, let's go into Genesis 15 and
five. Tell you what the Lord what was
going on here.
Genesis 15.
>> Okay. 15 and verse 5 says, "And he
brought him forth abroad and said, look
now toward heaven and tell the stars if
thou be able to number them." And he
said unto him, "So shall thy seed be."
>> Now you'll see going to be like, like
the stars in heaven. You can't number
them. Now, let's go into Jeremiah 30. to
Genesis 13 and read verses 14- 16.
>> Okay. Genesis 13 verses 14- 16 says,
"And the Lord said unto Abram, after
that Lot was separated from him, lift up
now thine eyes, and look from the place
where thou art northward and southward,
and eastward, and westward. For all the
land which thou seeth, to thee will I
give it, and to thy seed forever. And I
will make thy seed as the dust of the
earth, so that if a man can number the
dust of the earth, then shall thy seed
also be numbered.
So in short, the Lord is telling them
that you cannot number
Abraham's seed or you cannot number
Israel. and David cuz they going to be
like the sands of the seas. That's the
way the Lord used terminology. Just like
you can't number the stars, you can't
number the sands of the seas or the dust
of the air. You cannot number Israel or
Abraham's seed. So, so David in counting
them
was kind of like counter a counter uh uh
contrary to what God had said. So, that
was an abomination cuz he said, "I can't
number."
So that why it was an abomination in
Joab's eyes and God didn't like it. So
the Lord said just like the sands of the
sea, stars of heaven, you cannot number
Israel because it going to be so many or
Abraham seed. That's all I have to say.
>> Thank you for that guest caller. We hope
you got the answer for your question.
Sister Deborah, let's move on.
>> Moving on. Be alert says people use
scriptures to justify wearing crosses.
Uh be alert gives Hebrews 12 verse 2,
Luke 14 verse 27 and says there's other
scriptures. Can you please provide
scripture to disprove this lie about
wearing crosses?
>> Yeah. Let's let's go to Exodus 20 and
we're going to read verses 4 and 5.
>> Okay?
>> Uh because the cross is a graven image
that people bow down to, kiss, pray
with.
It is a graven image. Let's see what the
books say. Exodus 20 verses four and
five. Go ahead, brother. Thou shalt not
make unto thee any graven image, or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above, or that is in the earth beneath,
or that is in the water under the earth.
>> Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them,
nor serve them. For I, the Lord thy God,
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me. You see the thing is this
is a graven image. The cross is not a
symbol of of righteousness or praise.
The cross is a symbol of death. And many
people were d uh uh unal alived died on
the cross. Jesus wasn't the only one in
the last 2 million years. The book tells
us that the crosses would never bear
that. It was up to 500 people a day
crucified.
So, no, the cross is a death symbol and
it is a graven image. So, I I hope that
that helps. That's all I got on that.
Sister Deborah, next question.
>> Yeah, next question. Stevens Valentine
Senior asks, "Is there any scriptures to
explain what happened to the jaw of mana
and Aaron's rod that budded yet
missing?" And first Kings 8 verse9 is
given.
>> We're going to ask brother Julius to
answer that question. Brother Julian,
>> I haven't seen anything but this right
here. Let's go to Hebrews the 9th
chapter. We know that Aaron's rod was in
the uh ark and we know that the jar of
mana was in there that he fed Israel
with for 40 years.
Hebrews chapter 9, James
and read verse
3-5.
>> Okay.
>> Hebrews 9.
>> Hebrews 9 and verse 3 to 5. When you get
it, go ahead, brother. And after the
second veil, the tabernacle, which is
called the holiest of all, which had the
golden sensor, and the ark of the
covenant, overlaid round about with
gold, wherein was the golden pot that
had mana, and Aaron's rod that budded,
and the tables of the covenant, and it
>> of the covenant. Go ahead. And over it
the cherubims of glory shadowing the
mercy seat of which we cannot now speak
particularly. We cannot speak
particularly.
So we don't have only thing we see is
what John said in his vision what he
saw.
This is all we can revelation revelation
11 chapter.
Revelation 11 chapter
and read verse 19. Revelation 11 and 19.
This the best we could do with that ark.
Revelation 11 and 19. Go ahead.
>> And the temple
>> vision. This is John vision. Go ahead.
>> And the temple of God was opened in
heaven. And there was seen in his temple
the ark of his testament. And there were
lightnings and voices and thunderings
and an earthquake and great hail.
>> That's all we that's all we know about
the John Mana and the errands ride that
buddy. The book don't give detailed info
on that.
That's all I got. Dre.
>> Thank you, brother Julius. Uh, Sister
Deborah, next question.
>> Next question. Zion Israel says, "If
we're to get baptized starting at 20,
why did Jesus wait until he was 30 years
old?" And Luke 3:es 21-23
is given.
>> We're going to ask the guest caller to
answer that question. Guest caller,
>> read Luke 3:21
23 baptism.
>> Okay. Luke 3 and 21-23 says, "Now when
all the people were baptized, it came to
pass that Jesus also being baptized and
praying, the heaven was open, and the
Holy Ghost descended in a bodily shape
like a dove upon him, and a voice came
from heaven, which said, "Thou art my
beloved son. In thee am I well pleased."
And Jesus himself began to be about 30
years of age being as was supposed the
son
of Joseph which was the son of Hel.
>> Listen whole thing is 20 is when the
Lord hold you responsible. But if you
want to enter into the ministry you have
to do it from 30 to 50. That is the law.
Let's go into numbers the fourth
chapter. Sir,
>> read one one to three and we're going to
skip down and read verse 22. Well, 1 to
three first.
>> Let me know when you finish.
>> Okay. Numbers 4:1-3 says, "And the Lord
spake unto Moses and unto Aaron, saying,
Take the sum of the sons of Kohath from
among the sons of Levi after their
families by the house of their fathers,
from 30 years old and upward, even unto
50 years old, all that enter into the
host to do the work in the tabernacle of
the congregation." That was the end of
verse three.
>> End of verse three. So the so these are
priests. Get down to another because
it's because the Levites are the
priests. Skip down to verse 22 and 23.
Another one uh Levi's son. Go ahead.
>> It says, "Take also the sum of the sons
of Gershon throughout the house of their
fathers by their families. From 30 years
old and upward until 50 years old shalt
thou number them all that enter in to
perform the service to do the work in
the tabernacle of the congregation.
>> Go to another set of priests 29 to 30.
>> Okay. It says, "As for the sons of Mary,
that thou shalt number them after their
families by the house of their fathers,
from 30 years old and upward, even unto
50 years old, shalt thou number them,
everyone that enterth into the service
to do the work of the tabernacle of the
congregation."
>> Okay. And now the last seven, 46-47.
All those that were numbered of the
Levites, whom Moses and Aaron, and the
chief of Israel numbered, after the
families, and after the house of their
fathers, from 30 years old and upward,
even unto 50 years old, everyone that
came to do the service of the ministry,
and the service of the burden in the
tabernacle of the congregation.
Now, it's because the law said if you
going to enter into the ministry, you
have to be 30 years old. And if you
older than 50, you can't enter into the
ministry. That don't mean you can't
serve God. So, being responsible, the
Lord held us responsible because he said
when we come out of Egypt, oh, all
Israel murmured against God. And God
said, "Well, I tell you what, I ain't
going to I'm going to breach my promise.
I'm not going to let all of you murmurs
into the land, promised land.
Everybody from 20 years old and upward
except for Joshua and Jayla is going to
die in the wilderness and let us know
that that's when he held them
responsible from 20 years old and
upward. But when it come to the
priesthood, priesthood, that's a
different thing all together. Being
knowing that being responsible and be
and becoming a priest are two different
things. That's all I have to say. Thank
you. Guest caller made plain for you.
Uh, Sister Deborah, time check.
>> Yes, the time is 811.
Zion asks, "What's what is the
difference between the white Gentiles
and the white people that's supposed to
be Esau that's in Jerusalem? Aren't they
still the white man?"
>> We gonna ask Brother Julius to answer
that question. and brother Julius.
>> No. No. They're not the white man. All
you got to do is go to your local
hardware, your your major stores, and
look at the pink section. There's at
least 150 different shades of white.
Esau came out red and and hairy
and Jacob came out black. But let me
show you something here. They are Esau
is they had come out of Noah's son Shim.
Genesis chapter 5. I'm sorry. Genesis
chapter 10.
>> Mhm.
>> Genesis 10.
And these are your European nations and
their sub people that come out of them.
Pick it up at verse one. James, we going
to read 1 to five quickly. Go ahead.
>> Okay. Now these are the generations of
the sons of Noah, Shim, Ham, and
Japheth. And unto them were sons born
after the flood.
>> Uhhuh.
>> The sons of Japheth, Golar, and Magag,
and Maidi, and Jan, and Tubal, and Mach,
and Tyrus.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the sons of Gomer, Ashkanaz, and
Rith, and Togamar.
and the sons of Javan, Elisha, and
Tarsus, Kdum, and
>> Dodin.
>> By by these were the owls of the
Gentiles, divided into their lands,
everyone after his tongue, after their
families and their nations.
>> Now, these are what you call what we
commonly call white people or Europeans
and their descendants. Now,
Esau
had as Jacob's twin brother. It's just
that one came out of Red and Harry and
Genesis the 25th chapter and the other
didn't. But they are twins but not
identical twins. So, they came out of
Esau came out of Shim. The Gentiles or
Europeans came out of Noah's son Jac. I
hope that helped.
Go in the 25th chapter of Genesis and
read it.
>> Okay.
>> I'm there.
>> Genesis chapter 25.
>> 25 picking up at verse 19. Pick it up at
verse 19 and 20. Go ahead and read.
>> Okay. And these are the generations of
Isaac, Abraham's son. Abraham begat
Isaac. And Isaac was 40 years old. And
he took Rebecca the wife, the daughter
of Bethwell, the Syrian of Padanaram,
the sister to Lean, the Syrian.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And Isaac entreated the Lord for his
wife because she was barren. And the
Lord was intreated of him. And Rebecca
his wife conceived.
And the children
>> And the children struggled together with
her within her. And she said, "If it be
so, why am I thus?" And she went to
inquire of the Lord. And the Lord said
unto her, "Two nations are in thy womb,
and two manner of people shall be
separated from thy boughs, and the one
people shall be stronger than the other
people, and the elders shall serve the
younger."
>> Continue. And when her days to be
delivered were fulfilled, behold, there
were twins in her womb. And the first
came out red and all over like a hairy
garment. And they called his name Esau.
>> That's what the name Esau mean. The name
Esau mean red. Go ahead.
>> And after that came his brother out. And
his hand took hold of Esau's heel. And
his name was called Jacob. And Isaac was
three score years old when she bare
them. So you got two different nations,
but they got the same parents, but
they're not Gentiles. They come out of
uh Noah's son, Shim, which is where
Abraham. Uh so this these are the
children. They're Abraham's seed and
they're both Hebrew. One is a Hebrew
Edomite and the other is a Hebrew
Israelite.
Anything else we add to that guest
caller?
>> The white man is a gentile.
>> There you go. people all come out of two
different sons of Noah. That's it.
>> That's right.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Thank you, brother Julius and
guest caller, Sister Deborah. We're
going to go to the next question.
>> Next question. Gary Sanderson says,
"There was a question previously asked
if Solomon repented.
Can we glean anything from 1st Samuel 7
14 and 15 regarding that question?
>> Let's go to 1st Samuel uh verse uh
chapter 7 vers 14 and 15 and read that.
>> Okay,
>> go ahead.
>> It says
>> go ahead brother. And the cities which
the Philistines had taken from Israel
were restored to Israel from Echron,
even unto Gath. And the coast thereof
did Israel deliver out of the hands of
the Philistines. And there was peace
between Israel and the Amorites. And
Samuel judged Israel all the days of his
life.
>> Yeah, this this particular scripture has
nothing to do with that at all. So the
answer is still no. But I think you were
talking about 2 Samuel. So let's just go
there. 2 Samuel 7
14 and 15.
>> It says I will be his father and he
shall be my son. If he commit iniquity,
I will chasen him with the rod of men
and with the stripes of the children of
men. But by but my mercy shall not
depart away from him, as I took it from
Saul, whom I put away before thee.
>> Mhm. Go ahead.
>> And thine house and thy kingdom shall be
established forever before thee. Thy
throne shall be established forever.
Now, this one that he's talking about,
his throne will be established forever.
And notice he said, "I will be his
father and he shall be my son." This is
not talking about Solomon in that sense.
Now, let's go to Hebrews the first
chapter. Hebrews the first chapter.
Hebrews 1 and verse 5. Read that when
you get it, brother. For unto which of
the angels said he at any time, thou art
my son? This day have I begotten thee?
And again, I will be to him a father,
and he shall be to me a son. He didn't
say it to none of the angels, but he did
say it to Jesus. So the scripture that
you read that you asking about is
talking about Jesus. Now, let's go one
other place. Let's go to Luke the 1
chapter and we gonna read verses 31-33.
Luke the 1st chapter 31-33.
Go ahead when you get it, brother.
>> And behold, thou shalt conceive in thy
womb, and bring forth a son, and shall
call his name Jesus.
>> He shall be great, and shall be called
the Son of the Highest. And the Lord
shall give unto him the throne of his
father David. And when he shall reign
over the house of Jacob forever, and of
his kingdom there shall be no end.
>> So this was talking about Jesus, the
scripture in Samuel that you was talking
about, not Solomon, because Solomon's
kingdom did not reign forever. And we
still don't know the answer to that
question. And we cannot assume. There's
no scripture that says
whether Solomon repented or not. That's
all I got on that.
Sister Deborah, let's move on to the
next question.
>> Moving on. Brother Anthony Horsey has
two questions. First one, 2 Corinthians
6 and 7.
Um
he wants to know what is this
ministration of death written and
engraved in stone. And the second
question is in the same uh book 2
Corinthians 3-16
concerning the veil that covered the
face of Moses. Well, let's go to that 2
Corinthians 3 verses 6 and 7 and then
verses 13 and 14 and we'll ask the guest
caller
>> uh yeah 13- 16 we'll ask the guest
caller to answer that question.
>> Okay. 2 Corinthians 3:es 6-7 says, "Who
also hath made us able ministers of the
New Testament, not of the letter, but of
the spirit. For the letter kleth, but
the spirit giveth life." But if the
ministration of death written and
engraven in stones was glorious, so that
the children of Israel could not
steadfastly behold the face of Moses for
the glory of its countenance which glory
was to be done away.
>> Okay. Now, first thing is let's
understand what ministration of death
is. We weren't supposed to be no death.
Now, let's go into Psalms chapter 82.
Psalms 8, chapter 82. And we're going to
read 1 and two. And then we're going to
skip down and read six and seven. One
and two first.
>> Okay. Psalms 82:1 and2 says, "God
standeth in the congregation of the
mighty. He judgeth among the gods."
How long?
>> Mhm. on the first thing is he said he's
standing in the congregation of the
mighty and he judges among the gods days
they but two in the godhead right now
that is the father and the son so who
are these gods we going to show you that
he's talking about man and what he is
supposed to be read the next verse
>> how long will ye judge unjustly and
accept the persons of the wicked
>> now that's the question so because we
did. Look what happened. Get down
verse uh uh six and read six and 7.
>> Verse six says, "I have said ye are gods
and all of you are the children of the
most high, but ye shall die like men and
fall like one of the princes."
Okay. So now we weren't supposed to die.
But since Adam and Eve sin in the
garden, God brought in death and we have
been under administration of death ever
since. Even though the command because
the commandments had to come. Now first
we had one in one commandment not to do
something and that's to stay away from
the tree of the knowledge of good and
evil. The Lord said if you because if
you go and eat of that tree you going to
die. We ate of it. He said now we are
dying. We are under the ministration of
death. Now let's go into the Exodus the
34th chapter
and we're going to read verse one. Then
we're going to skip down to verse 28 and
read to verse 35. Go ahead.
>> Okay. Verse 34 and or Exodus 34 and1
says, "And the Lord said unto Moses, cue
thee two tables of stone like unto the
first, and I will write upon these
tables the words that were in the first
tables which thou breakest."
>> Now, this is the word that was etched in
stone. Okay, skip down to verse 28 and
continue.
>> And he was there with the Lord 40 days
and 40 nights. And he did neither eat
bread nor drink water. And he wrote upon
the tables the words of the covenant the
ten commandments.
And it came to And it came to pass when
Moses came down from Mount Si with the
two tables of the testimony in Moses's
hand when he came down from the mount
that Moses wise not that the skin of his
face shone while he talked with him.
And when and when Aaron and all the
children of Israel saw Moses, behold,
the skin of his face shone, and they
were afraid to come nigh him. And Moses
called unto them, and Aaron and all the
rulers of the congregation returned unto
him, and Moses talked with them.
And afterward all the all the children
of Israel came nigh, and he gave them in
commandment all that the Lord had spoken
with him in Mount Si. Until Moses had
done speaking with them, he put a veil
on his face. But when Moses went in
before the Lord to speak with him, he
took the veil off until he came out, and
he came out and spake unto the children
of Israel that that which he was
commanded. And the children of
>> Uh-huh.
>> Go ahead. And the children of Israel saw
the face of Moses that the skin of
Moses's face shone. And Moses put the
veil upon his face again until he went
in to speak with him.
>> So now the children of Israel could not
look on Moses because his face was
shining. Like Paul said, they could they
could not uh uh uh look at the to the
end of what we are supposed to come
are supposed to become rather they
cannot look at look to it and see what
our end results are. Let's go and show
you now. This is what mo was happening
to Moses. He was starting to make the
change. First go to 1 Corinthians the
15th chapter.
We're going to read verse 49 to 54.
1 Corinthians
vers 49
>> to 54 says
and as we have borne the image of the
earthy, we shall also bear the image of
the heavenly. Now this I say, brethren,
that flesh and blood cannot inherit the
kingdom of God, neither do corruption
inherit incorruption.
Behold, I show you a mystery. We shall
not all sleep, but we shall all be
changed. in a moment, in the twinkling
of an eye, at the last trump. For the
trumpet shall sound, and the dead shall
be raised incorruptible, and we shall be
changed. For this corruptible must put
on incorruption, and this mortal must
put on immortality.
So when this corruptible have or when so
when this corruptible shall have put on
incorruption and this mortal shall have
put on immortality
then shall be brought to pass the saying
that is written death is swallowed up in
victory
>> and that terminates the administration
of death is when the Lord come and Moses
has started to make the change but And
the people couldn't look at it. That's
why he had to put a veil over his face
because the change was setting in. But
the Lord said he going to remove the
veil said over the whole world. Not just
what Moses what what Israel said, what
Paul says. Skip, let's go to m uh uh uh
uh Isaiah the 25th chapter. We're going
to read verse one and skip and and then
skip down and read verse seven and 8.
>> Okay. Isaiah 25:E1
says, "Oh Lord, thou art my God. I will
exalt thee. I will praise thy name for
thou has done wonderful things. Thy
counselss of old are faithfulness and
truth."
Then verse, you said verse 5 through
seven,
>> seven and eight.
>> Oh, seven and eight.
>> Seven and eight. And he will destroy in
this mountain the face of the covering
cast over all people and the veil that
is spread over all nations. He shall
swallow up death and victory. And the
Lord God will wipe away tears from off
all faces. And the rebuke of his people
shall he take away from off all the
earth. For the Lord has spoken it. Now
the veil that he going to remove from
the face of all people not just Israel
and what is that what's that veil false
doctrine but in Israel's case where Paul
is talking about the veil was over over
uh uh uh Israel to this day he was
talking about as a people because under
the old covenant there was several
things that Israel was doing that uh was
terminated one of them is the uh uh uh
is the animal sacrifice. Let's go and uh
uh read some of that right quick cuz
let's read 13 and 16 from uh now go back
to what was that? Uh this the last part
of that was 13 and 16.
>> Yeah, that was 2 Corinthians
13-16.
>> Okay, read that those two verses. It
says, "And not as Moses, which put a
veil over his face, that the children of
Israel could not steadfastly look to the
end of that which is abolished." But
their minds were blinded. For until this
day remainth the same veil untaken away
in the reading of the Old Testament,
which veil is done away in Christ. But
even until this day, when Moses is read,
the veil is upon their heart.
Nevertheless, when it shall turn to the
Lord, the veil shall be taken away.
>> So now he said he could not look of
Israel could not look to the end of that
which was abolished because at the end
of this flesh and blood form, we going
to be spirit beings and we're going to
shine. Didn't it tell you when Jesus
took the apostles in the mountain, he
was transfigured and he say shine like
what?
>> Like the sun.
>> There you go.
>> So they they couldn't stand and look at
our end results what we going to be
beings of light.
But now as far as the rest of it is
concerned, the veil still was over
Israel because Jesus died but most
Israelites didn't believe in him.
Pharisees and the Sadducees didn't
believe in him and still they don't. And
so they kept doing the same thing,
animal sacrifices. And some of them
don't do the animal sacrifice no more,
but they still blowing the uh uh blowing
the chauffeur and they got certain
riches that they go through. Let's go
and show you what I'm talking about.
Because now in Jesus time, we are under
the new covenant. Let's go in, excuse
me, in the Hebrews the 10th chapter and
we going to have a look at this
because uh there was a lot of things
under the old covenant, you know, like
he over there talking about the red heel
and the sprinkling and all that kind of
stuff. We don't do that no more. But
Israel did it uh uh uh until we got
driven out the land. That's why it was
such a big fight and persecute of the
apostles.
But the Lord made a new covenant. That's
10 and1. Hebrews 10:11 verse
>> for the law having a shadow of good
things to come and not the very image of
the things can never with those
sacrifices which they offer year by year
continually make the comers there unto
perfect.
Now
the animal sacrifice wasn't the only
thing that was terminated. We had
marriage thing that was terminated. We
had priests that you go to if a if a man
was uh uh was accused his wife of
adultery, he had to bring her in and uh
uh uh get dust off the floor and make a
solution and if he eat it, she eat it.
If she was guilty, her bowels would fall
out. It's all kind of stuff where you
certain washings of you had to do before
you eat. All kind of ritual that went
with animal sacrifice because none of
them could remove sin. Skip down to
verse four and read to 10.
>> For it is not possible that the blood of
bulls and of goats should take away
sins. Wherefore, wherefore when he
cometh into the world, he saith,
sacrifice and offering thou wouldest
not, but a body hast thou prepared me?
And burnt off in burnt offerings and
sacrifices for sin thou has had no
pleasure.
Then said I, lo, I come in the volume of
the book, it is written of me to do thy
will, oh God. Above when he said,
sacrifice and offering and burnt
offerings and offering for sin, thou
wouldest not, neither hath pleasure
therein, which are offered by the law.
Then said he, Lo, I came to do thy will,
oh God. He has taken away the first that
he may establish the second by the which
>> now what he took away. He took away the
old covenant that he might establish the
new covenant. And when did that new
covenant come into existence? At the
death of Jesus. Read that.
>> By the which we w by the which will we
are sanctified through the offering of
the body of Jesus Christ once and for
all.
Now, that put us under the new covenant.
Now, skip down to verse 15 and read to
18.
>> Whereof the Holy Ghost also is a witness
to you. For after that he had said
before, this is the covenant that I will
make with them after those days, sayeth
the Lord, I will put my laws into their
hearts, and in their minds will I write
them, and their sins and iniquities will
I remember no more. Now where remission
of these is, there is no more offering
for sin.
>> Now what happened is when Jesus died,
you come under the new covenant that
terminated an animal sacrifice that
terminated the solution with the red
heer
and you don't kill no more lambs on
Passover. But what you do is he took one
thing out of the old covenant and
brought it to the new and that was his
commandments. Even like to this day we
have Edom over there
want to restart animal sacrifice and
will and we have brothers that know who
that we are Israel and they eating lamb
every Passover instead of taking the
bread and wine. Those are the ones that
the veil whose face the veil is still
over. That's all I have to say.
>> Thank you guest caller for that light.
We hope that you got some understanding.
Sister Deborah, let's go on to our next
question.
>> Next question. Marcus Kimbro asks, "Are
Mexicans in the Bible? And if so, who
are they? And is there anything biblical
about them getting sent back to their
own country?"
>> We're going to ask Brother Julius to
answer that question. Brother Julius,
>> everybody is in the Bible. Everybody's
in the Bible. Let me show you. Let's go
to Genesis chapter nine.
Mexicans are Gentiles. They're on the
European continent. They are
Castellians,
Spaniards.
Genesis 9, read verse 18 and 19. Brother
James. Genesis 9 verse 18 and 19.
Everybody on this earth is a descendant
of one of three of Noah's sons. One of
three of Noah's sons, Shim, Ham, and
Let the book tell you. Go ahead.
>> And the sons of Noah that went forth of
the ark were Shim, Ham, and Japheth. And
Ham is the father of Canaan.
>> Go ahead.
>> These are the three sons of Noah, and
them was the whole earth overspread.
>> Read that again, brother. Read that
verse again.
These are the three sons of Noah, and of
them was the whole earth overspread.
>> There you go. Everybody that's living is
a descendant of one of Noah's three
sons, Shim, Ham, or JFat.
So therefore, Mexicans are Gentiles.
They're on the European continent. that
we said uh at least two or three times
in this uh episode, Gentiles are
European, what we call white people.
They might be a different color of
white, but they still Gentiles
and their land and they and they are
Castellians. That's why the book said
after their tongues, in their lands,
after their nations, he said that about
all of three all three of Noah's sons.
So they are Gentiles and they fall up
under the children of Japet in Genesis
10 1-5.
That's all I got. And by the way, uh
your other question, what's the other
part of that, Deborah?
>> The other part was anything biblical
about them getting sent back to their
own country?
>> Everybody is going to go back to their
own country. Let's go to Isaiah the 13th
chapter.
Everybody come from somewhere.
Isaiah 13, Brother James.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay.
>> And let's read verse 13. Let me hold on.
Let me get it here.
Uh Isaiah the
13th chapter and pick it up.
[Music]
Pick it up in verse 13. Isaiah 13 and
13. This is the when the Lord come. Go
ahead.
>> Therefore, I will shake the heavens and
the earth shall remove out of her place.
>> And the wrath of the Lord of hosts and
in the day of his fierce anger.
>> Go ahead.
And it shall be as the chase row, and as
a sheep that no man taketh up,
>> they shall
>> they shall every man turn to his own
people and flee everyone into his own
land.
>> And this is yet future when the Lord
come back. Everybody go back to where
they are. Everybody going to go back to
where they are, where they originated
from, the way that God put it uh in the
creation. So therefore, that's the best
we could do with that.
Thank you for that, brother Julius.
Sister Deborah, next question.
>> Next question. Markeel Jackson says,
"According to Genesis 10, we learned
that the children of Shim are the Hebrew
Israelites, blacks in America. We
learned that the children of the
Gentiles are the Europeans and white
people. Who are the Hammites? the isles
of
>> well the Hammites are let's let's go to
Genesis 10 and I want you to Julius just
broke down how by Noah I mean by by the
sons of Noah was the whole earth
overspread so we going to read verse one
and we'll skip to verse six to answer
your question Genesis 10 verse one,
brother, and then skip to six.
Go ahead.
>> Okay. Verse one says, "Now these are the
generations of the sons of Noah, Shim,
Ham, and Japheth, and unto them were the
sons born after the flood."
>> Verse six says, "And the sons of Ham,
Kush and Misra, and Foot and Canaan."
So these are the the sons of Ham are
what you call today most of your African
nations that you got Misreion which is
Egypt,
Canaan and Put and Kush. So this is the
descendants that came out of Ham, Noah's
son. That's where Ham's descendants came
from. I mean the the sons of Ham are
these. That's all I got on that. Sister
Deborah, next question. Yes, next
question. Uh Sandra Herring,
uh
we would like for uh your question on
trying to understand marriage. We would
like for you to resubmit your question
by rephrasing your question on marriage
because it is too vague. So please
resubmit your question on trying to
understand marriage. We are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday,
August the 6, 2025.
Shaquille A Joby asks or says, "I
understand Jesus is God, but can you
please explain these two scriptures?"
Mark 15:34
and Mark 13:32.
Who was he speaking to? And why doesn't
Jesus know the time if he is God? So the
scriptures are Mark 15 verse 34 and Mark
13 verse32.
He wants some explanation on those two
scriptures.
>> So we'll read those scriptures, brother
James, and then we'll open it up to the
panel. Mark 15 verse 34 is the first
scripture.
>> Okay. It says, "And at the ninth hour
Jesus cried with a loud voice, saying,
Eli, Eli, Lama Sabathani, which is being
interpreted, my God, my God, why has
thou why hast thou forsaken me?"
Let's go over to uh the 13th chapter now
and read verse 32 and then we'll open it
to the panel
>> that says but of that day and that hour
no man knoweth or no man know not the
angels which are in heaven neither the
Son but the Father.
open to the panel.
>> What's the question again?
>> The question is he states, "I know that
Jesus is God, but they want some
explanation
on those scriptures on who was he
speaking to
and why doesn't Jesus know the time if
he is God?" So, who was he speaking to?
Matthew 13 and verse one.
>> Okay.
>> And and then in that 15th verse, in that
15th uh chapter at verse 34, he was just
he's just making a statement crying out
to fulfill the scriptures. My God, my
God. We're fulfilling Psalms
uh uh everything that were wrote about
him. But Matthew 13 and pick it up at
verse one.
>> Okay. Matthew 13:11 says, "The same day
went Jesus out of the house and sat by
the
>> I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Mark
13."
>> Okay. Mark 13 and1 says,
>> "And as he went out of the temple, one
of his disciples saith unto him, Master,
see what manner of stones and what
buildings are here."
>> So he's talking to his disciple, one of
his disciples, right?
>> Mhm. man. Continue.
>> And Jesus answering said unto him,
"Seeth thou these great buildings? There
shall not be left one stone upon another
that shall not be thrown down."
>> Now you can read the whole thing, the
same exact thing scripture in Matthew
the 24th chapter. It's just coming from
Mark's point of view. Now look what they
said in verse four and then we'll move
on.
Tell us when shall these things be and
what shall be the sign when all these
things shall be fulfilled?
>> At verse three it says Peter, James and
John asked them privately. He's talking
to his disciples. All this is talking
about his disciples and he's telling
them uh uh at verse 32 now.
But of that day and that hour no man
know not the angels which are in heaven
neither the son but the father
>> right he said knoweth no man right need
heaven the father know the fathers the
book says what it says but we know that
we know when Jesus coming back we know
according to if you read the rest of the
previous scriptures we know the great
tribulation got to come we know that the
seventh trumpet got to sound We know
that the man of sin got to sit on this.
So we we understand the signs of the
times. That's why he said when you see
the abomination it make it desolate. So
we know that the vows and the seals got
to come. We know we know these things
that's got to come. But you know them by
reading the scriptures.
>> Okay. Can I intervene?
>> Yes sir. Go ahead.
>> What was the first what would he what
did he ask the first time?
The first question was who was he
speaking to and the second one and why
doesn't Jesus know the time if he is
God?
>> Now the first thing is he was speaking
to the one that he always spoke to.
Let's go into Genesis the first chapter.
Start reading at verse 26.
>> Okay. Genesis 1 and verse 26 says, "And
God said, let us make man in our image,
after our likeness, and let them have
dominion over the fish of the sea, and
over the fowl of the air, and over the
cattle, and over all the earth, and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the earth."
>> Now, he said, Now, he said, "Let us make
man in our own image," didn't he? Right.
>> Yes.
Now keep reading.
>> So God created man in his own image and
the image of God created he him. Male
and female created he them.
>> Now so this was Jesus talking to the
father.
That's who he was talking to. Now let's
go into uh uh Zechariah the second
chapter.
>> Zechariah 2.
>> Uhhuh.
Okay,
>> let's see where we going to pick it up
at.
Zechariah 2 and let's see
uh let's start it at start at verse one.
Okay. Zechariah 2 verse
>> go ahead.
>> It says, "I lifted up mine eyes again
and looked and behold a man with a
measuring line in his hand."
Then then said I, "Wherether goest
thou?" And he said unto me to measure
Jerusalem, to see what is the breadth
thereof, and what is the length thereof?
And behold, the angel that talkth with
me went forth, and another angel went
out to meet him, and said unto him, and
said unto him, Run, speak to this young
man, saying, Jerusalem shall be
inhabited as towns without walls for the
multitude of men and cattle therein.
For I sayeth the Lord will be unto her a
wall of fire round about and will be the
glory in the midst of her.
>> For I say the Lord, I'm going be the
roll around. Right. Go ahead.
>> Ho ho, come forth and flee from the land
of the north, sayeth the Lord. For I
have spread you abroad as the four winds
of of the heaven, sayeth the Lord.
Deliver thy deliver thyself, O Zion,
that dwelleth with the daughter of
Babylon. For thus sayeth the Lord of
hosts, after the glory hath he sent me
unto the nations which spoiled you. For
he that toucheth you touches the apple
of his eye.
>> Look what it said. For thus said the
Lord of hosts, say what? after the
>> for thus sayeth the Lord of hosts, after
the glory hath he sent me unto the
nations which spoiled you. For he that
toucheth you toucheth the apple of his
eye.
>> The Lord of hosts telling you he was
sent.
Is this what they're saying?
>> Mhm.
>> Keep reading. For behold, I will shake
my hand upon them, and they shall be a
spoil to their servants, and ye shall
know that the Lord of hosts has sent me.
>> Go ahead. Now, he said, "I won't shake
my hand over the nation, and you shall
know that the Lord of hosts have sent
me." Go ahead.
>> Sing and rejoice, O daughter of Zion,
for lo, I come, and I will dwell in the
midst of thee, sayeth the Lord. And many
nations shall be joined to the Lord in
that day, and shall be my people. And I
will dwell in the midst of thee, and
thou shalt know that the Lord of hosts
has sent me unto you. And the Lord shall
inher.
[Music]
He was talking to the one that became
the father.
Cuz Jesus was doing all the talking. Go
to St. John 6 and read verse 37.
>> Six and
>> 5 and 37. I'm sorry. 5 and 37.
>> Okay. 5 and 37. John 5 and 37 says, "And
the father himself which has sent me
hath borne witness of me. Ye have
neither heard his voice that it said the
father himself have sent me have borne
witness of me." Go ahead. Ye have
neither heard his voice at any time nor
seen his shape.
>> Now that let you know that Jesus was
talking to the father
St. John the 17th chapter and starting
verse one.
>> Okay. John 17 and verse one says
these words spake Jesus and lifted up
his eyes to heaven and said father the
hour is come glorify thy son that my son
also may glorify thee
>> as thou has given him
>> Mhm.
>> Go ahead. as thou has given him power
over all flesh, that he should give
eternal life to as many as thou has
given him.
>> And this is and this life eternal, that
they might know thee, the only true God,
and Jesus Christ, whom thou has sent.
I have glorified I have glorified thee
on the earth. I have finished the work
which thou gavest me to do. Mhm.
>> And now, oh father, glorify thou me with
thine own self with the glory which I
had with thee before the world was.
So Jesus was talking to the father. Even
then he was in the garden of Eden.
That's why Adam and Eve said we heard
your voice in the garden hid ourselves.
Because Jesus always talked to the
father. Let us make man in our own
image. So that's what he was talking to
the father. But go read that second part
again of this question.
>> The second part of the question again
was who was he talking to and why
doesn't Jesus know the time if he is
God?
>> Go read it.
>> Okay. What what scripture was that
again?
>> Mark 13 verse 32.
>> Mark 13.
And verse 32, Mark 13 and verse 32 says,
"But of the but of that day and that
hour knoweth no man. No, not the angels
which are in heaven, neither the Son by
but the Father."
>> Okay. So if Jesus God, you say he didn't
know that? I read that because I want
you to go and ask Jesus that soon as he
is. What is he talking about? If Jesus
heals God, I want you to go to Hebrews
the first chapter and see what God
called it.
>> Hebrews chapter one.
>> Mhm.
And we going to start it at and talk
where it's talking about the until the
uh first begotten.
>> Okay. You want me to start at uh verse
four or you want me to start at verse
one and read that?
>> Verse six.
>> Verse six. Okay. He wants to go straight
there. And again. And again when he
bringeth into mean and again when he
bringeth in the first begotten into the
world he saith and let all the angels of
God worship him.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Keep going.
>> And of and of the angels he saith who
maketh his angel spirit and his
ministers a flame of fire.
>> Keep going.
>> Go ahead. But unto the Son he saith,
"Thy throne, oh God, is forever and
ever. A scepter of righteousness is the
scepter of thy kingdom." Go
>> ahead.
>> Thou thou hast loved righteousness and
has and hated iniquity. Therefore, God,
even thy God, hath anointed we anointed
thee with the oil of gladness above thy
fellows.
>> So what did God call it?
>> God.
>> God. Now go to St. John the first
chapter and start reading at verse one.
>> Yes. Okay.
>> It says, "In the beginning was the word
and the word was with God and the word
was God. The same was
>> what?
>> Was God."
>> Go ahead.
>> The same was in the beginning with God.
>> All things.
Listen. In the beginning was the word.
The word was with God. And the word was
God.
Let us go in Revelation the 19th chapter
and see who was called the word. 19 and
verse 11.
>> Yes sir.
>> Revelation 19 and verse 11 says and I
saw heaven open and behold a white horse
and he that sat upon him was called
faithful and true. And in righteousness
he doeth judge and make war.
>> And his and his eyes were a flame of
fire. And on his head wore wore many
crowns. And he had a name written that
no man knew but he himself. And he was
clothed with a vesture dipped in blood.
And his name is called the word of God.
>> Yes sir.
>> Bless Jesus.
Is that talking about Jesus?
>> Yes sir.
>> In the beginning was the word. The word
was with God and the word was God.
Now, if you want to know why that Jesus
didn't know, whoever asked the question,
I suggest you write that down as soon as
you see Jesus, you ask him. That's all I
have to say.
>> Thank you for that guest caller, Sister
Deborah. We got a couple of minutes
left. Let's get in one or two more
questions.
>> All right. Uh the next one is from
credit account. uh credit accounts said
when Iogg did black history IOG had a
slide of the felashes in Ethiopia and
they refer to themselves as Jews. How
come they did this when they are out of
the tribe of Dan?
Open up.
>> Guest caller. Go ahead.
>> What did he say? They were Jews. They
said they was Danites.
>> So, let him give the evidence where they
said that they was Jews.
>> All right.
>> All right. We got enough for one more
question. Sister Deborah,
>> and it's referring to Dan again. Barbara
Still said, "According to your knowledge
in the Bible, why does Dan why was Dan
erased from the 12 tribes of Israel?"
>> Dan wasn't erased from the 12 tribes of
Israel.
You can't exclude a tribe. It must be
Let's go to Revelation.
What is that? Seven.
Revelation,
>> James, Revelation 7
and pick it up at verse one. Okay.
Revelation 7:1 says, "And after these
things, I saw four angels standing on
the four corners of the earth, holding
the four winds of the earth, that the
wind should not blow on the earth, nor
on the sea, nor on any tree."
>> Uh-huh.
>> And I saw another angel ascending from
the east, having the seal of the living
God. And he cried with a loud voice to
the four angels to whom it was given to
hurt the earth and the sea.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Saying, "Hurt not the earth, neither the
sea, nor the trees, till I have sealed
the servants of our God in their
foreheads."
>> Uh-huh.
>> And I heard the number of them. I heard
the number of them which were sealed.
And there were sealed 144,000
of all the tribes of the children of
Israel
>> of 11 tribes
>> of all the tribes of the children of
Israel.
>> So because Dan is not mentioned
evidently is some sort of typo but the
book tell you of all the tribes of
Israel.
And that's what was a type.
>> That's a typo he gave cuz he had Ephraim
in there and then he had Joseph.
But Joseph is the father of Ephraim and
Manasseh. Okay.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Typos,
>> right? And 12 * 12 is 144,000.
All the
>> That is right. So it was a typo.
>> All right, Sister Deborah. Time check.
Yes, the time is 9:02.
>> Okay, we like to thank everyone who sent
in all those questions from around the
world,
>> took joy in answering them and pray that
you were edified. If you didn't hear
your question answered tonight, there's
no need to resubmit your question. It
will be answered in the order that it
was given and we will pick it up where
we left off next week. So, please join
us for next week's Q&A and be
strengthened in the word of the Lord.
Brother James, close us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven. Give us this day our daily
bread. And forgive us our debts as we
forgive our debtors. And lead us not
into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen. Hey.